veevr.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Veevr

Mille Media Limited is committed to protecting your privacy when you use Veevr.com. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. It is very important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms set out in our Privacy Policy, please do not use Veevr.com.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any revisions will be effective upon posting the new Privacy Policy on the Veevr website at [http://Veevr.com/privacy_policy](http://veevr.com/privacy-policy/). We will advise you that changes have been made by posting a notice on our website or otherwise. Your visit to or use of Veevr constitutes your acceptance of the terms of our Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding Veevr's policies or practices relating to privacy, please direct them to [support@veevr.com](mailto:support@veevr.com)

**Last updated on October 30th, 2011**

## Collection of Information

While using Veevr you may gather information on our website, view, publish and download video or other content, share, comment on or post information, subscribe to one of our services, join groups, or participate in other activities available throughout Veevr.com. In doing so, we may collect certain information about you. Mille Media Limited stores your E-mail, Date of Birth, Location and Password you create for yourself when you register with Veevr.com and any other details if they are indicated in User Profile. We also use your IP address for internal purposes (for covering the user sessions). We may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of Veevr.com, like the number of users and frequency and manner of usage of Veevr. We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our subscription-based services, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by Veevr and our third-party advertising providers during your use of Veevr and in serving advertisements to our website, including, for example, the number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information).

We may collect and/or you may choose to post profile information about your interests, groups or affiliations, your videos, photos, personal statements, or other information about yourself. We may collect and/or you may choose to post personally identifiable information when you seek access to certain portions of Veevr.com, when you view, publish or download content, and/or register for or participate in our services. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address, software and hardware attributes, type of computer and credit card or other payment information. Please be aware that if you disclose personally identifiable information in your profile or when you post comments or publish videos, the information may become publicly available.

## Use of Cookies

We may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer hard drive so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We use cookies to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

## Third Party Cookies

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Third party advertisements displayed on or in connection with the Veevr website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. We do not control these cookies and users of Veevr should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether and how it uses cookies.

## Use of Information

Aggregated information that we collect is used to better understand how Veevr.com is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you. Aggregated information, as well as other non-personal information is also used by Veevr.com and our advertising providers to facilitate and monitor the serving of advertisements. For more information about Google Ad Manager, cookies, and how to opt out, please go to http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. In addition, the cookies that are used by Veevr.com and its advertisers are used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage other third parties to monitor the usage of, and serve advertising to Veevr.com. These third parties may use cookies and web beacons (which collect non-personally identifiable information regarding user behavior on our website) to collect such information, which is also used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies you may be unable to access certain services and features of Veevr.com. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

## DoubleClick DART cookies

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google.s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (.interest based targeting.). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses .non personally identifiable information.. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx).

We may also use information about you and your activities on our website to customize your experience and to customize the content or features of Veevr.com and for the purpose of tailoring the online advertising you may encounter. We may use your personally identifiable information to fulfill your requests for services, to communicate with you about your account, to support your online activities, and to respond to your questions. We may use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to Veevr.com, the Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may also use your personally identifiable information and/or your profile information to personalize your interactive experience on Veevr.com. For example, if you have given us permission, we may use your information to inform you of other Veevr and/or third-party products or services you may find valuable. We may also use the information you provide to make improvements that better serve our users' needs.

To edit your personal information that you entered when you created your account or make changes to your profile information, you must log-in to Veevr.com and click your Account Settings at the top of any page to manage your account and adjust your settings. If you prefer not to receive information about additional products and services, you can choose not to receive this information by opting-out. 

## Disclosure of Information 

We may share aggregated statistical information and profile information about users of Veevr.com with third-parties, including our distributors, vendors, advertisers actual and potential customers, business partners and third-parties that offer products or services for use with Veevr.com. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Veevr.com will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties, with the following exceptions:

  1. Your name or screen name may be available through search indexes.
  2. As necessary to third parties who perform services for us in operating and marketing Veevr.com, included but not limited to the monitoring of user behavior on our website and the processing of payments for products or services. 
  3. We may be obliged or deem it necessary or appropriate to disclose your information in certain special situations. These situations include: in response to legal process such as a court order or subpoena; to prevent or combat fraud; as required by federal or state law; enforcement of our Terms of Use; and protection of the rights, property or safety of Veevr.com, our users or others. 
  4. In the event that Veevr.com is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Veevr.com may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used. If you access any third-party applications, follow links from the Veevr.com to another website, or view Veevr.com from another website, the information you disclose may no longer be covered by this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to check whether other privacy policies will govern before you release any personal information.

## Security 

Veevr.com is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. Veevr.com uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information. But please keep in mind that you are solely responsible for safeguarding the secrecy of your password.

While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data.

## Young Children 

We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website. For more information on how to protect your child's privacy, you can visit the Federal Trade Commission's Kidzprivacy page, accessible via www.ftc.gov.

## Opt-Out

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).) Veevr.com provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us regarding products and services in which you may be interested. If you do not opt-out at the time you provide information, but choose to opt-out later, you may un-select these options from your account settings page. We reserve the right to send you administrative message, service announcements, and other similar communications without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

## Modification of Privacy Policy

Veevr.com reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
